<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rejectionReasons>
	<rejectionReason>
		<name>Although you may be suitable for the funding that we offer, the competition for places was such that we were not able to progress your application on this occasion. </name>
	</rejectionReason>
	<rejectionReason>
		<name>Although you may be suitable for your preferred course of study, the competition for places was such that we were unable to progress your application on this occasion. </name>
	</rejectionReason>
	<rejectionReason>
		<name>At the present time, we are unable to a supervisor to support you in your preferred course of study. </name>
	</rejectionReason>
	<rejectionReason>
		<name>At the present time, we are unable to allocate a supervisor to support you in your preferred course of study. </name>
	</rejectionReason>
	<rejectionReason>
		<name>We are no longer able to offer your preferred course of study. </name>
	</rejectionReason>
	<rejectionReason>
		<name>We are unable to form a judgement on your suitability based upon the information that you have supplied in your application. </name>
	</rejectionReason>
	<rejectionReason>
		<name>You failed to present for interview as arranged.</name>
	</rejectionReason>
	<rejectionReason>
		<name>You have informed us that you no longer wish to be considered. </name>
	</rejectionReason>
	<rejectionReason>
		<name>Your application was not considered eligible because the research that you intend to conduct is not within the remit of our funding. </name>
	</rejectionReason>
	<rejectionReason>
		<name>Your application was not considered eligible because you have not been admitted to your chosen study institution. </name>
	</rejectionReason>
	<rejectionReason>
		<name>Your application was not considered eligible because your student fee status has been determined to be overseas. This means that we are not able to award you with funding. </name>
	</rejectionReason>
	<rejectionReason>
		<name>Your application was not considered eligible. This will be because: (a) your application for study at your chosen institution was unsuccessful; (b) your fee status has been determined as Overseas, and/or; (c) Your research falls outside or our remit.</name>
	</rejectionReason>
	<rejectionReason>
		<name>Your qualifications and experience are not appropriate for your preferred course of study.</name>
	</rejectionReason>
	<rejectionReason>
		<name>Your qualifications and experience are not sufficient to satisfy the entrance requirements for our organisation. </name>
	</rejectionReason>
</rejectionReasons>
